export const quizCompetitionstate = {
  questions: [
    {
      questionNo: 1,
      question: "What is the result of the following expression: 5 + 3 * 2?",
      options: ["11", "16", "13", "9"],
      answer: "11",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 2,
      question: "Which of the following is NOT a JavaScript data type?",
      options: ["String", "Number", "Boolean", "Float"],
      answer: "Float",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 3,
      question:
        "What is the correct syntax to select an element with the id 'myElement' using JavaScript?",
      options: [
        "getElementById('myElement')",
        "querySelector('#myElement')",
        "$('#myElement')",
        "document.getElementById('myElement')",
      ],
      answer: "document.getElementById('myElement')",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 4,
      question: "What is the result of the following expression: '2' + 2?",
      options: ["22", "4", "TypeError", "NaN"],
      answer: "22",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 5,
      question:
        "Which of the following is the correct way to declare a JavaScript array?",
      options: [
        "var colors = [];",
        "var colors = {};",
        "var colors = ();",
        "var colors = '';",
      ],
      answer: "var colors = [];",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 6,
      question:
        "What does the 'typeof' operator in JavaScript return for the 'null' value?",
      options: ["object", "null", "undefined", "boolean"],
      answer: "object",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 7,
      question:
        "Which method is used to add new elements to the end of an array in JavaScript?",
      options: ["push()", "unshift()", "concat()", "splice()"],
      answer: "push()",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 8,
      question:
        "What is the output of the following code? console.log(3 + 2 + '7');",
      options: ["12", "327", "57", "37"],
      answer: "57",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 9,
      question:
        "Which JavaScript method is used to remove the last element from an array?",
      options: ["pop()", "shift()", "slice()", "reduce()"],
      answer: "pop()",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 10,
      question: "What does the '!=='' operator in JavaScript mean?",
      options: [
        "Not equal in value",
        "Not equal in value and type",
        "Equal in value",
        "Equal in value and type",
      ],
      answer: "Not equal in value and type",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 11,
      question: "What is the purpose of the JavaScript 'map()' method?",
      options: [
        "Iterates over an array and applies a function to each element",
        "Checks if at least one element in an array satisfies a condition",
        "Returns a new array containing elements that pass a condition",
        "Reduces an array to a single value",
      ],
      answer: "Iterates over an array and applies a function to each element",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 12,
      question:
        "What is the output of the following code? console.log(3 + 2 + '7');",
      options: ["12", "327", "57", "37"],
      answer: "57",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 13,
      question:
        "Which JavaScript method is used to remove the last element from an array?",
      options: ["pop()", "shift()", "slice()", "reduce()"],
      answer: "pop()",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 14,
      question: "What does the '!=='' operator in JavaScript mean?",
      options: [
        "Not equal in value",
        "Not equal in value and type",
        "Equal in value",
        "Equal in value and type",
      ],
      answer: "Not equal in value and type",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 15,
      question: "What is the purpose of the JavaScript 'map()' method?",
      options: [
        "Iterates over an array and applies a function to each element",
        "Checks if at least one element in an array satisfies a condition",
        "Returns a new array containing elements that pass a condition",
        "Reduces an array to a single value",
      ],
      answer: "Iterates over an array and applies a function to each element",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 16,
      question: "What does the '&&' operator in JavaScript represent?",
      options: ["Logical AND", "Logical OR", "Logical NOT", "Assignment"],
      answer: "Logical AND",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 17,
      question:
        "Which method is used to convert a JavaScript object to a JSON string?",
      options: [
        "JSON.stringify()",
        "JSON.parse()",
        "object.toString()",
        "object.valueOf()",
      ],
      answer: "JSON.stringify()",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 18,
      question: "What is the purpose of the JavaScript 'forEach()' method?",
      options: [
        "Iterates over an array and applies a function to each element",
        "Checks if at least one element in an array satisfies a condition",
        "Returns a new array containing elements that pass a condition",
        "Reduces an array to a single value",
      ],
      answer: "Iterates over an array and applies a function to each element",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 19,
      question:
        "Which built-in JavaScript method is used to round a number to the nearest integer?",
      options: ["Math.ceil()", "Math.floor()", "Math.round()", "Math.abs()"],
      answer: "Math.round()",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 20,
      question: "What does the '||' operator in JavaScript represent?",
      options: ["Logical OR", "Logical AND", "Logical NOT", "Assignment"],
      answer: "Logical OR",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 21,
      question:
        "Which method is used to check if a JavaScript string contains a specific substring?",
      options: ["includes()", "indexOf()", "startsWith()", "substring()"],
      answer: "includes()",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 22,
      question: "What is the purpose of the JavaScript 'filter()' method?",
      options: [
        "Creates a new array with the results of calling a function on every element",
        "Checks if at least one element in an array satisfies a condition",
        "Returns a new array containing elements that pass a condition",
        "Reduces an array to a single value",
      ],
      answer: "Returns a new array containing elements that pass a condition",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 23,
      question: "What is the result of the following code? typeof typeof 42;",
      options: ["number", "string", "undefined", "TypeError"],
      answer: "string",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 24,
      question: "Javascript is an _______ language?",
      options: [
        "Object-Oriented",
        "Object-Based",
        "Procedural",
        "None of the above",
      ],
      answer: "Object-Oriented",
    },
    {
      questionNo: 25,
      question:
        "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
      options: ["let", "const", "Both A and B", "None of the above"],
      answer: "Both A and B",
    },
  ],
};
